100free.com 2002-06-04

# 100Free.com

| 

_Home_ ****

 ********

**What this Privacy Policy Covers**  

  * This Privacy Policy covers 100Free.com's treatment of personally identifiable information that 100Free.com collects when you are on the 100Free.com site, and when you use 100Free.com's services. This policy also covers 100Free.com's treatment of any personally identifiable information that 100Free.com's business partners share with 100Free.com. 
  * This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that 100Free.com does not own or control, or to people that 100Free.com does not employ or manage. 

**Information Collection and Use**  

  * 100Free.com collects personally identifiable information when you register for a 100Free.com account, when you use certain 100Free.com products or services, and when you enter promotions or sweepstakes. 100Free.com may also receive personally identifiable information from our business partners. 
  * When you register with 100Free.com, we ask for your name, email address, and other geographical information. Once you register with 100Free.com and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. 
  * 100Free.com also automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, 100Free.com cookie information and the page you requested. 
  * 100Free.com uses information for three general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see on our pages, to fulfill your requests for certain products and services, and to contact you about specials and new products.
  * 100Free.com uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. Our third-party advertising company also separately places or recognizes a cookie file on your browser in the course of delivering advertisements to this Site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please [click here](http://www.sonar.com/content/privacy.htm). 

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**  

  * 100Free.com will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone. 
  * 100Free.com will send personally identifiable information about you to other companies or people when: 
    * We have your consent to share the information; 
    * We need to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested; 
    * We need to send the information to companies who work on behalf of 100Free.com to provide a product or service to you. (Unless we tell you differently, these companies do not have any right to use the personally identifiable information we provide to them beyond what is necessary to assist us.); 
    * We respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process; or 
    * We find that your actions on our web sites violate the 100Free.com Terms of Service or any of our usage guidelines for specific products or services. 

**Cookies**  

  * 100Free.com may set and access 100Free.com cookies on your computer. 
  * 100Free.com allows other companies that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to 100Free.com's cookies. 
  * 100Free.com uses web beacons to access our cookies within our network of web sites and in connection with 100Free.com products and services.

**Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences**  

  * 100Free.com gives you the ability to edit your 100Free.com Account Information and preferences at any time. 
  * You may request deletion of your 100Free.com account by sending an email to [support@100free.com](mailto:support@100free.com). 

**Security**  

  * Your 100Free.com Account Information is password-protected for your privacy and security. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**  

  * 100Free.com may edit this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our pages. 

**Questions or Suggestions**  

  * If you have questions or suggestions send an email to [support@100free.com](mailto:support@100free.com).

**** F.A.Q.    |   Policies   |   Features   |   Privacy   |   Support   |   Sign Up

| 

 Fast, Reliable, Free Hosting!

* 40 Megs of Free Web Space!
* Unlimited Bandwidth Usage!
* Multiple Directories Allowed!
* Live Tech Support!
* Friendly Site Manager!
* Super Fast Internet Connections!
* Webmaster Resources!
* Corporate and Personal Accounts!
* Now With FTP Access!
* Click Here To Sign Up! 

 Become A Member Free!!

|
